https://www.marcrist.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who are Marcrist?
Marcrist are a multi-national group headquarters in the UK specialising in the manufacture and distribution of diamond cutting tools and diamond systems solutions for professional users.
We are committed to securing your personal data and to prevent the misuse of personal data. We have policies detailing how we will protect your personal data and we will never share your data with third parties.
Organisation name: Marcrist International Limited
Reference: Z5417707
How do we use your personal data?
There are various purposes for which you give us your personal data, including to keep you up-to-date with our products and to enhance your experience on our digital platforms.
Full details can be found in our data protection policy.
What personal data do we use?
Data given directly through filling out a contact form, via email, telephone or social media.
Data collected automatically through website cookies, social media and analytical plugins.
Data from already public sources, for example your social media profile.
Data from an application for a job with us.
What are cookies and plugins?
Cookies are small text files stored on your device containing details about your online activity.
Plugins are software from digital service providers to provide social media integration in our website.
We use cookies and plugins to enhance your user experience of our website.
What is the purpose?
Your personal data is used to provide news, product updates, events and to improve our offering. You can update your communication preferences at any time or unsubscribe completely. We will not send you email without your consent.
Further information
You can find more details on our cookie policy.
